So, we begin, we study Nagarjuna, his
name is Arya Nagarjuna, sometimes they just
call him Nut, he is the most famous Arya in
the history of Buddhism, he lived 800 years ago,
I think he was a co-author of the Yoga Sutras
because I consumed a lot of things that I later
regret, all from the time of
Nagarjuna, that's how the era of
Christianity began, maybe 200 years after
that, I think there is some connection with
Christianity, a follower of Thomas,
who is a follower of Jesus, he came
from India
from a place called Sila, he
worked for a king whose name is Gandho
Faris, the novel and romances call him
Gaspar, King Gaspar and the Three Kings was
Tomato, he worked, it was part of
Yandiev, then now this part of
Afghanistan, I think there was some connection,
Thomas himself is from India,
Vodara, so finish, and that place is still there,
he was killed there
[music]
all this place in India is now
Christian Kerala, Christian and
Nagarjuna came from that place from the south of
India, bandages new, his place where he was born
and  The monastery is the greatest monastery, a
farm from the airport, Bingo Dur, you
pass by this place instead of
Nagarjuna's house. He is from South India. He is the
greatest teacher according to the article, and this is
his greatest book on emptiness, which is
called wisdom. He
wrote 10-15 books, and I taught in
Guangzhou in the greatest company.
Guangzhou government mountain
from Villian. I was very interested. If you are
interested, talk to her. She knows all this. A
cool program called The Path of
Kings. We are going to study wisdom,
which is the greatest book. It became the
basis for all explanations of emptiness. Every
country, Japan, Korea, China,
India, Tibet, and every place where you can
study simplicity, you study Nagarjuna.
You study his works. I thought it would be
great to just spread
this for several years. We
will study wisdom for ten days. We do
this once a year. There are 3
comments, which we will use
one of Jason Kopy's comments, and
perhaps this is the greatest comment
on Nagarjuna. It is called the ocean.
Emptiness Rick rise tell me
have to and therefore evidence of
emptiness I like to call the book the
ocean of emptiness and a short name it was
written by Jung Oppa if we translate
we will translate this this all day 5 250
2500 pages Jung Oppa it's quite
difficult and another teacher is a black lama
1175 thousand seven hundred something and these are
difficult comments
but this weight without diarrhea cannot be learned this is
difficult at all not impossible that
is difficult but not impossible
if you go out first read menila we
will start with black break it is about 1000
1000 pages of translation which theoretically
as god everyone can do for our
team we have done 3 3 bedrooms
thousands of pages a year that is we can
here we have time if we don't have to
waste time
on fun and all sorts of nonsense if someone
else can we can raise money
so that we can study gives
us
oh I could study for a day what she
lama then it would be
cool because then
I would not be a learned lama but we  must do
both but we must do
both because I can't do both
so help me
please don't come after and don't say don't ask don't
ask me
how to help just a few thousand makes
us several thousand dollars we
need money to finish the book
translation is hard work it's a lot of
work but this place is so cool if
we can finish the roads here and 7 we won't
finish the road it's high health
height not very dangerous they are not
covered with alpha asphalt yet and they are very
dangerous and because they are getting narrower
and narrower and I don't want someone flying a
car from the mountain
so help us let's figure
this out if you figure it out you decide that
you will do it there are many of them
from different places and different countries we can
do it it's not impossible don't think
I'm not a magnet
we made this building we made another
building it's nothing so much money we
can do this heart but we have to
try that is you each need a
ship ship
dream cops to cross the ocean it's
quite difficult you need a ship
to cross the ocean of
emptiness and then why didn't the lama write
to Kyiv which is called a ship
which you can use to
cross the ocean of emptiness, it's a
little joke, he's talking about Tsongkhapa's book, I
want to be the captain of the ship, I just
take my book, we'll cross,
pu bag with you, let's not a problem, and we're
going to finish the commentary with
ink, a difficult moment, this is called
difficult moments in wisdom,
we will also use these
comments, the greatest comments on
Nagarjuna
Chandra Kirta, 650, his book
is called the
descent to the middle path,
2 comments, one is called the entrance to the
middle path, the hamster's mat,
avatar models,
and the second book is called about Santa, under
which means what does it mean, an explanation of the
words of subsidence, a fireplace for that, comments
about which explains the words of wisdom,
which wisdom and in this book and the
entrance, the entrance to the middle path,
explains their meanings, also this, both
books, they are about this teaching in any country, the
EU, which you did not come to, Vietnam, China,
Korea, books came from them, these are comments
that were translated by other
translators, Chinese, real name
Ivanchuk, who is more likely, and he distributed all these
books, her
Japanese books too, and these are very, very
powerful books, this is because these are not these, this
book
spread, came to  We need this
exact curtain and probably called it
simply wisdom, which Sanskrit me
through the day one Russian Russian
Russian holiday correct pronunciation
as I know I know this same
pronunciation is the most correct brother of the day
close to Sanskrit I know we had it filmed to remove, which
means I know super knowledge
wisdom of Nagarjuna the book is called
simply wisdom sun so he said
let's just modular for this what would be
studied and the first question
homework it says what a ship is,
but according to the article you can cross this
ocean of emptiness we need how the ship
itself to cross it Chunya Lama offers
such a ship and we will give you a notebook
where you can write everything down and 55
pages
explanation of the lion dance we will give you these
explanations they are about everything developing they are the
basis of the teachings of Maitreya jewel
realization without Alan Khara himself
very famous lines are taken from there
strongly like Singapore sing-sing apparatus
this occurred drain Sen Katala lion you
Singaporeans I love and this is what we are
going to study all our books
ship to the sea of ​​emptiness just  I'd like
to remind you how many courses we have at the
top 5,
just try to come to each
of them. I get upset when we
have to repeat. Different people
come from. It's hard for me to teach 55
people who are
new, so I have to
repeat. This is understandable. If you haven't
built the roads, then you should
come and build. We already covered 2
eyes from the head in the first course last
year. At this time, we covered the first two
chapters. There are so many parts. 2727 very
famous parts of the
eyes, and we studied these very eyes. The
structure of the chapters. How Nagarjuna chose to
teach emptiness. His nickname is Arya. The
Markovians call him never.
[music] The
city of Beijing is called something. China is
now the largest city in the world. The
simplest one calls it the largest city, and
also the army is simply called Arya, because it is the
largest. And if you are from Mexico,
we just say we are from Mexico. Mexico is
this city. Mexico City.
They don't say Mexico City. So, we
finished the first eye. By
the way, I have a new cool idea.
Yesterday,
deaths, the day before yesterday. I want to teach you.
When we study Sanskrit, wisdom, I
want you to learn the most important words.
When you study,
you will be given
Sanskrit words to do your homework.
Then you will learn thirty to forty
words from Austrian, and then you will
say, "Savior Kotova, we will arrive in pairs, I'm
afraid, Indonesian link language, it
was very heavily based on Sanskrit,
it seems, and we will use
Sanskrit words, you should study them a little,
we will study the violin
words in every class, in every lesson,
pariksha, tell me, pariksha,
I will tell you two things from homework,
number one, I included these words in my
homework and they have a meaning
there and there is a root of this word, guys, which
came to English like her, these are
words that came from Sanskrit and from
Sanskrit to English almost
unchanged, they are called k lamb, what k
gnits stand like this, like days for days, I
know, I know this when and that's why in
English there is gay before before before
science should be know the east, I know I
knauf it came from about two there was
j
it came from Sanskrit she  It changes to
KEY, it's a strange spelling, so in
English KEY is in front of N.A.W.
It's days. If you know these Koblenz,
then you can study Sanskrit,
remember it easily. What's important? Look,
all the Buddhas spoke Sanskrit. Why is
Squid important? All the Buddhas spoke
Sanskrit.
When will you become like that? You'll have to
speak Sanskrit, so
start now.
Or second, you can impress your
friends. You'll
find something like that at a party. If you go to K,
he impressed you. You know,
where did this channel come from? Why is there
hockey? I'll tell you, Nenko. It's not an alcoholic
party. Each chapter is called
Pariksha. Pariksha. Tell me, Pariksha,
this is your homework. Homework.
One or two Sanskrit words will be in the
test. I'm giving you this for free.
Homework from the explanation. The meaning and
cornice. You just need to fill in these
three. One of them will be in the
controller. Maybe a pair. There will be
Paris, and that means researching the question.
Analyzing the question. I like to
research again. Follow research.
Each chapter of wisdom is research.
We check. We check something. Some
question and this structure.
There for homework request homework
structure of wisdom pariksha
each chapter sk are called Paris and
research or investigation as
the police investigate
who killed this guy also investigates
book
structure of wisdom each cute is
pariksha
deceased means investigation first
thing is your homework first
thing someone will come comes up with a stupid idea
someone comes to you with a group of people like
my husband
yells at me for example in the kitchen because
he is tired he hasn't eaten yet and there
were traffic jams on the roads according to Buddhism this is super
stupid super stupid idea this is something and
yells so and my husband yelled at you today
because he is tired and I haven't done it yet
and he was stuck in traffic if you
want to write 25 chapters of wisdom you
can call them my husband in the kitchen and the
first sentence will be someone comes
and gives you struct
stupid ideas this structure all that is my
husband yells at me because he is tired he has
n't had dinner yet strong hasn't eaten
or bon at him the boss yelled at him ice
was in traffic someone will come and bring a
stupid idea
and then Nagarjuna will fight with  32
I want to see your
homework. His style is simplification and
his style is simple and
practical. He always uses
short poems, short, and he uses
ideas from the ordinary world. He uses ideas from
normal Ramira,
like in your homework. The last
things or homework are real
[music].
Real application. This is called
real application. And Nagarjuna
was very, very, very good. He was the
greatest philosopher of ancient India, and that
made him the greatest
because he brought it to the kitchen. He
always brought it to the kitchen. He
wasn't just philosophy. He
always brought it to the kitchen. Therefore,
your homework every day is a
real application.
You do it yourself. Order. A
real application exists. You don't
know how. Ask chaos.
He can teach you pills. Parties.
Look, shining. There is, and all this is a Kesha
course. You study it in the evening.
[music].
People started inviting me to how
to conduct a course and steam relationships about business.
What else should I have used
this course? Bald patches, so that it would be
clear, to find a way to
apply this in the kitchen in business, and 10
is real application.  That is, I write from 10 and 7 and
Takeshi
10 Takeshi course created for a second
husband for a war in the family or business
if you want to give money if I want
money and need for money because I
know real
[music]
ordered three years news from plans for
three years ahead I want to teach you
take 7 and make 10 out of it this is
called real about the best tvorimir son
jani pieces in China himself the best city in the
world and inferno now I think so and there is a
Chinese program for children
when this is very close now this is I'm going from here straight
there after give me motma
children Mr. Wood are there and you guys
from China
thank you for coming you will go there
and right here right now I bread I said I
can't teach with me I can't teach with
me I'm very busy I have so many things I have to
do
8850 and 850 pages for Alice
I'm losing hair vision Brady says
two things happen first hair you lose something
something
I'm very
stressed out from your ears, I'm not ready at all to go, details, I
immediately, what should we do, and I decided, I'm the army of
the wall and Alice, we'll organize them so they
write a course, they will create a course, we
told them, come on, guys, you take the
material and you will do it, or olap, and
they went to a translator course, we
translate the greatest books of all time,
and there will be 8,000 pages of translation, and
they came to the industries and to the
translator course, and then they themselves had to
make their own app,
and you will teach the next one, the
next husband, the second husband, in the kitchen,
next time, the first thing you do
in 5 years, you look back and
realize that five years ago you were
absolutely stupid and
made mistakes, this is normal, but this is just you,
from we learn, he has made the
greatest app, cool, very
red, talk to them, you know,
how do you do each damage, it should
include this idea of ​​​​emptiness and make it
and the area,
how can I include it in real life, people
ask how I am, you are like this, I studied 2
span 1000 business strategies, I didn't just
sit in  I studied food and in the desert, I studied the kind of
strategy, and so who will do it, and before,
first it was Nagarjuna and he made
reals, his style was he took a guy who, for
that stupid questions, the old man went to do
and an investigation for every stupidity, a
person came and then an investigation of
normal reals from there comes and then the
black lama came and says it wasn't
very done nor Torshin, this came from an
ancient conversation of Buddha and he begins
to talk about sultry for each pair of lice,
that is, in each chapter, 3 things happen.
Number one, someone comes and says
something stupid like my my husband is tired,
so he screams and me, why is he
actually screaming? What did you yell at your
children last week? This is the real
reason. 1. He was really
stupid, second, this is a real application,
then you take and real write-offs of tea to
us and says, however, don't you think that
Nagarjuna invented this and it all comes
from the Heart Sutra. The
black lama in structure
3 he says that this comes from
Buddha from the speech of water.
Nagarjuna refers to the future and quotes
him. oh no, what is not  Lama
Tea Lama Quotes Stop Talking
Held the
First Three Heads and We Finished Chapter 1 2 3
Called Investigation of Conditions Factors
Factors Hack One Thing Makes
Another Thing Happen This is
Chapter 1 Chapter 2 For 10 Dollars
Like a Stone When Going When a Whim
Comes and Comes and Goes
10 Dollars Lemon Singapore His Wife Red
Chapter 2 How Do You Come How Do You Go How Do
You Go What Coming Happens When
You Come and Go When I Walk
Through the Door What Really Happens
When I Walk Through the Door A
Picture Jumps Out of My Myoma
Small Picture More More Door
More Door More Wear Big Door
Then I Walk Through the Door Less Door Less
and Less Door Less I Don't Walk I
Don't Walk Through the Door Pictures Pictures Pictures Pictures
[Music]
We Call It Walking Hangs They
Pass Devils Where Sheela Never
Walked Through Any Door
Picture Small Big Big More More
Door Less Tver Less
Light Less Tver
We Call It Walking Nagarjuna Says
This Is Not a Real Question
on Gare Du  nord it's not
true that this is actually
happening and it's unreal it's not
real
when you see an ordinary door like you
and the so-called  Atlanta,
give me Nagarjuna's answer, how did you get to
Diamond Mount? You gave other
people rides before, that's all. You didn't come here
by car, you didn't come here by
plane. You didn't drive on the road. You
gave other people rides, gave other
people rides, and this is real. This is real.
Flying on a plane isn't real. This is
n't what's happening. It's just a husband
screaming because he's tired. This is
n't real. You understand. This is Chapter 2,
Chapter 3. Happily, we're studying 6 chapters. This
time, six chapters.
Chapter 3 is short. Chapter 4 is
short. How many did I say
we're studying? 6. Glass, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, and 8. So,
your homework is the longest
question,
which isn't in the tests? You don't even have to
study it. You can give me the name of
Paris and
these chapters. Pieces of a wig, a couple,
another guy, a better guy, Farah. This is all around.
When you find English, how is it not
always gay? It
changes to "and" in Sanskrit. It often
changes to "and" in English, so
such a guy is like a periscope.
Perimeter.  pen and don't take me, this is the guy
from
periscope, you can do everything around,
perimeter, this means boundaries around the place in front of everything around them, he
knows, look,
look, and this came from Germany
[music]
becomes shark, this is the word for eye, ocular,
optometrist about atom, 3rd, these are
these words,
a lot of English, English eyes,
came and
oh, happened there, and oh, comes from
kick, shy, pair, and the USA, which means check everything
around, explore around, investigate,
everything, investigate, what, who investigated, 20
dollars, who investigated, no, and
you, the word, gave initiation for 20 dollars,
who was investigating cases, the investigator, and
therefore, who investigated in this book,
seed, no, Jason, cap-cap, he is a researcher, what are they
investigating, that's what, what is investigating the
void, the last, last chance,
Nagarjuna Arena, Kopchenov, a researcher,
what are we investigating, all my money was canceled,
canceled the money, we can spend the
whole day like this, he is investigating this,
this stupid guy, my husband, and my husband is
angry, he swears at misery all the time, he
yells because he is tired, he had a
bad day, let's investigate this
Let's follow what you're saying. The
first guy who comes in each
chapter is big, he's the subject of the
investigation. Let's check. It's burning. They're upset,
so let's check. Why are you wrong?
Each head is called a
ball. USA. Then it's real. They'll solve it
because it's a guy, and USA 2 and 2 are
made longer, so Paris is
irradiated. I want to investigate. I'm
going to investigate this. So, Chapter 3.
Investigation of the powers of the senses. Eyes,
ears, and nose. Mouth. Heart. In the morning, we must
investigate. Eyes, ears, nose, tongue, body, and mind.
And we always go from top to bottom. We go from top to bottom.
First, the eyes, and then
us, then the mouth, then the body. Because we're
investigating the powers of the senses.
Tell me, what about the powers of the senses?
Indriya. Indriya Yan means power. The power of the senses.
There is no session of
Crimean words, and so on. Don't blow your
mind. Indriya. Tell me, this means Asia.
Where am I from? In the Ryazan books, Indra
means Indra. This is the name of God. This is power. This is a
very strong person.
English: Ivan
Vint. I win. I affirm.  The game for
comes from Indra, Dra's superpower, Indra's
superpower, the power of the eyes, the power of the mind, the power of the ears, the
whole village, the mouth, they have power, and here
we go to the text of Suganki, this is the
deepest text in this chapter, and think about the
wheel of life, the stove on the package, your
power of the senses, your equipment to explore, to experience this world without this equipment, you cannot touch things, you cannot do anything, you must check where the power of the interior comes from, such as not me, I defeat them, I have a village, Indra, God's power, silhouette 7, so we are
going to
investigate the forces why two reasons
are your homework, all your
homework, even your lunch, your
local work, just kidding, first,
Buddha taught for
51 years, a huge number of books that
Burda recorded, there are hundreds and hundreds of his
lectures,
they are divided into three wheels of
life, part 3 of his life, 1 1 is called the
boring period of Buddha's life,
sleep, heaps, 1918, categories, 474 truths, they are
all sorts of numbers, there, as if he counts
some period of calculations, such and simple, a
long list,
now these  Guys, in the first period of
life, they will write about this set 7, number
17, this is number 18, let's write about [ __ ] mouse
Stanley, the table in front of us, Stalin,
here he will do a binary translation, this
was the first, the first teaching of Buddha in the world,
then the second period of life, a warrior, think about
people, people just made a list, let's
teach them with brushes, Hyun Jin Chung, Jane,
heart court, once in the morning, diamond,
limited,
this is all the second period of his life, that in the
third period, the guy of emptiness happened, there is,
when they met, these two
parts of the meetings, and he said, and they
met, the one who wrote the sheets and the one
who wrote the emptiness taught according to the article, and they
began to wait, but what about according to the article, you don't
teach according to the article, forget the descents and
which they had a struggle among themselves like
10 and themselves, people, let's ask, I sewed
better, let's make a meeting, I was in a hurry, he
said,
he will tell us what is more correct, a waste of
time on foot, hung, should be a judge, I
will get, made a list, but everything is empty,
and they go when they are together, connected,
and this is the third turn  Wheels, school of
consciousness, only came from there, yes, they are together,
guys, this is all together, don't make
me a judge,
interact with each other, why did you
talk about this? Chapter 3, Chapter 4, Chapter 5.
They dig more often for this, more accurately, the
counter at 45,
this is for those people who love old
lists of
water, 5, a bunch of 12
organs, doors of senses, 18 categories, 4
truths of ari,
44,
12 links of the wheel of life. Chapter 3, Chapter 4,
Chapter 5. This is
all for this, under the counter, these are both
darmas who controlled Buddhism
for seven hundred years. Children,
these counters, the greatest Buddhists were for
seven hundred years. When will the world be, I do
n't know what happened. Guys who
conceived under the statue, perhaps they
simply meditated, and then these counters came under the counters
and spent seven hundred years with
Buddhism, then everyone loved both
darmas.
Buddhism simply became a religion while
counting or counting or mathematicians. There was a lot of
arithmetic, arithmetic, again, both darmas,
even drier than Darwin, DeMott, Mountain. I
went on, translated, and 12  years I'm serious
I know well two three 4 5 arithmeticians
came and we should what to do for them
pariksha for the dead and owe them ira must
investigate their yang they say stupid
things we will investigate like a
police investigation what do you think
chapter 3
taught the power of feelings how many of them 7 let's
investigate cases
eye contact blue blue color
and and the eyeball which determines
the blue color and which connects this all
will be in Buddhism this is appointed
called the power of the six senses six
objects it turns out 12 we see and hear and a
thing when you can smell touch feel
and then 6 fundamental
research wheels 1 rat of life these are the
powers of the senses indriya
and and I have Sanskrit for this so now what do
you think mathematicians came what they have
already said arithmetic what they say what do you
think he this guy arithmetic he
alone says that 10 dollars 675 now he is
not afraid of anything 44 dollars my
question what do you think there were lips stupid
things at the beginning of the chapter what the
arithmetician said this is happening on his part
100 dollars of this guy he  said
guys, I too, in fact, your eye
is looking at me too, you see me, you
have an eye, it works, it works from its
own side,
no need to tell me nonsense about
emptiness, Buddha said the power of the eye,
1 wheel of life, I'm not saying anything like that, I
already said what kind of stupid stub is stupid
nonsense about emptiness, look, the eye is
real, it sees, you can
track things and under them, cliff, come on, look,
you need an eye, it's real, it
works, the eye, we work, we don't tell you, I'm already
empty, not with stories, that it's not
real, what are you even talking about, are you
kidding me, Nagarjuna,
how are you looking at me, how do you use it,
explore, use your
eye, everything is empty, nothing exists,
then you can't see me, if everything is
empty, you can't see me, and the second
wheel, and then the turn of the wheel, why did you
spend so much time, spent so
much time teaching these 6
senses, this is how you communicate with the world,
acts of communicating with the world, these are super
real, supre real angles,
according to X, it has its own
power, why did he call it powers  Isn't this
power empty? Who is this? How do you
communicate with the world? This is chapter 3.
In each lesson we will go through one
main thing. I created the
lessons so that we go through chapters.
That is, you take one chapter, go home,
meditate, so that we have a bridge between
chapters.
Each chapter, each lesson, a little hub.
This is basically a chapter,
and basically, like previous chapters, the
next chapter, a little bit, that slaves, bridge
24.
Let's investigate the parts of a person. Know a
pile,
5 piles. Now, they say it's just body and mind. It's just body
and mind. Now, they say in
Buddhism, we say 5-ku, chit, the same thing.
You can call them
body and mind. You can call them five piles.
Why are 5 5 5 parts of a person called
5 piles? Why is 20 dollars cheap?
Chapter 1, both gifts, Makoshi Stanley. Well,
why are they called Pucci?
Why won't I say human happiness?
It's actually the same part of a person.
Why won't I say it? I didn't say piles.
Because you have to put everything
together and then they will work.
Good idea, but no, no, and 10 10 dollars.
Question: Some of  They are not physical and
emotional, no,
listen, just both of them, the so-
called ones, are launched because it is more concentrated.
The number of things is just a bunch of a large
number of things, you
can just think of them from a group of groups of
things, a person consists of two things, yours
ate the feeling of
separation, entertainment, and something else,
number four is called something else, and everything else, everything else,
sorry, all
countries, a body, many body parts, a
feeling, many abilities, the ability to distinguish, the
ability to mark, this is good, this is
bad, others, many abilities, strife,
divide, a lot of awareness, awareness,
awareness, this is a
finger pass, awareness, and the fourth and
last thing is everything else, chapter 4, in this,
we are going to
investigate the 5 parts of a person, so the
first pile, the first, the whole chapter, she
explores
your body because in the guy came,
Mr. Stupid Head came and says, in the
first three chapters, this arithmetician came
and says, look, 5 piles, says, 1 pile,
what a physical body, a physical body, you
tell me, it's empty, no, I didn't sleep, then do
you want me to hit you with my
real hand, we are learning, I hit it, it's an
unreal hand, then do you want me to hit you, it's all
empty,
and he says, look, it's super real, super
real, you can
feel it every day, you feed it every day, had,
feels, this body, this is
chapter number four, pariksha, body parts,
but we  Focus on wanted
Chapter 5 According to Buddhism and quantum
physics, the physical body is made of
energy of various energies
of gravity, electrical
weakness, weak charm,
electron neutrons, protons and other
things, chemists, chemists, chemical substances,
chemical elements, molecules, and scientists and
Buddhists say that all these are
elements, this is all chemistry in the body, these forces,
electricity,
gravity, could, you can, magnet, magnet,
magnetic force, all these are parts of the physical
body, I will, I taught this force,
sometimes they are called 18 on the graph, called
5,
female,
earth, water, fire, wind and space, these are the
five elements. In Buddhism, don't think
that they are some kind of stupid before people
learned about the phone and don't think that
when this force of gravity, the
force of electricity, they are very, they are very
deep. Don't think that the ancients
were stupid. There are six levels of
electrons, the 60th level of electrons. The first
part, both dorns, the
first chapter, binary, the second part
talks about this. The 5 elements are not
some things that scientists came up with,
that they are very, very deep about
energy and the body. If you go into his body,
you talk about chemical elements, the body,
how it works, what  what's so cool about
these elements earth-fire earth can
water fire
wind what's the coolest and space
focuses on the last coolest
space 5 bunch let's talk about the
first bunch physical last chapter
no chapter elements that create your
body let's talk the last
most interesting space what is
space what does it mean what is
space empty what chapter are we on 5
or 6 6 3 third asked and 4 pro
okay now we found the sixth chapter
[music]
desire and addiction we are going to
investigate desire addiction
Nagarjuna however
chat chapter 3 4 5 they are short because
I think on your feet it's not boring boring
to count he is already brief this is stupid this is stupid this is stupid this is
stupid let's move on to
something more interesting base like
desire for example it creates created
your body and elements let's talk about this
let's talk about emptiness and
desire its addiction
[music]
I'll give you the key there
when I first heard the title of the chapters and
then he will talk about 1
[music]
1 donuts got
that only green drink I drank nothing
interesting and we were in  I started
peeing
and the waiter brought a bunch of donuts
and I started giving it to everyone,
look, this is not green, this is
how delicious it is, this is a desire and then the
second part, I want, I want, I want this,
wait, this is no less, this is a symbol,
look at yourself, wait and then there is also the clutch, the
first desire, I have never
tried donuts and it requires a lot of
intelligence to grow up and yes, like
a child, actions, so, so, desire and
addiction, this is
not what the chapter is about, it looks like it
smells like that, novelty, this is not what the chapter is about,
so I'll tell you later, the correctness,
he and collect, he investigates here,
pariksha, what is desire and what is
addiction,
this is chapter seven, a very long chapter, the
second longest chapter, RD,
only one head and then there will be one
on either 4 true ones from the only one
that is longer,
but this is chapter 7, we are a super chapter, let's
investigate how things begin, how
things remain and how things stop, how things
begin, how things
continue and how things
stop, dad, darme, never
learned this in this order, why is he yelling with
berries, never taught in this order
300 dollars tell me why
10 9 8 7
65 okay canceled would be talentless
he always teaches beginnings
Astana stop and stay means
beginning stop and continuation beginning
stop and continuation why why
Buddha said so he didn't want you to
cling to stay continuation
continue was born you will die fool there
you are stay it's like that forget about
staying
think about how somehow born how
you will die and began about birth begin ends
remain it's
very short too short to
dwell on it and so chapter 7 talks
a lot about the beginning first idea by
darma it's not just beginning stops the
beginning has its own beginning with sentences its
own stop
how how the beginning begins let's
investigate this he just meets and the
tournament for against he wants to study the beginning beginning
and let's see how the beginning ends and
bream begins
stop
[music]
if this beginning has a beginning and this
beginning has a beginning no don't ask
me I'm just tired of this
provide me continues where the
beginning began
chapter 8
we are going to investigate who does
things only  who makes things and what and what
he does how things are empty and how people
do things and how you can eat your
breakfast what is my main focus of a
yoga class the most important thing breakfast we are
prime me and Brian we did it short
yoga cool class and a long-long lunch
how things begin how we personal things
[music]
how how is the person who makes
pots how does he make them these pots
because before he made pots
you called him a pot master how why how
at what point did a person
turn into a pot master
if before he made pots he
was not yet you cannot call a pot a
pot until you are not created
until it is made and then you look
while there is no pot how can you call the
person who you make a
pot master Nagarjuna's specialization he was
lucky specialization when it begins
but I will decide he says something is missing
something is not right here in this
picture this is his style that someone
comes and says he my husband yells at
me because he is tired hungry and
Nagarjuna,
something about this annoys me, what's not
there, and when we talk, the cook,
you say he's cooking food, it's just
beating me up, and you can't say that the cook is
cooking food
because a cook isn't a cook until
he's cooked the food. You can't
call a greenhouse a cook until he's caught sight of him, he has
n't cooked yet. When he is,
when can you call this
question because it hasn't happened yet? Yes, and it just irritates
me. Every Paris, and
it starts with you talking about some
stupidity, and he's like that, but it just
irritates me, so this stupidity of things. The world is
somehow strange for me. I think everything is wrong.
Something is going wrong.
You feed your husband. You give him
enough time to sleep, and there's
normal traffic, no traffic jams, but they're
blaming you, and there's something strange about
this, and everyone says something strange.
Something is happening. Something else should
be happening. It won't jump. It's not traffic jams,
it's not dinner. He's yelling at me,
in any case, something else. Here,
it's stylish, the bread is bitter. The people who
do this are somehow annoying.  I have something, something, this is
with Pariksha, we
need to check then here we start
with yelling at the children, what is happening
really 3 you yell at the children and this is his
style, this is the style of Nazar, what we just
finished raising to the sixth chapter
which we are going to study in these 10
days we will study 6 chapters om mani
padme hum monastery mani padme hum
means squeaked I hope maybe I
hope
[music]
what a common thing in these six chapters all the
objects we talk about they are all
fundamental to Buddhism
Buddha taught all this 18 books we translated in the
translation lesson in the translators' lessons 6 16
lessons are going on simultaneously in Sedona there are a
lot of books by De Velde but there is a
book by Stanley,
fundamental information there,
every book that
translates everyone complains about
Stanley's book about the book from the
site, everyone wants to translate the same book
that page sheet sitting in all the
books tantra where you Sklif tantra puts
either your year became bandhan we we we all  We
should always refer to his books. We
steal pieces from his books all the time
because it's fundamental.
It's the basis of Buddhism. These
arithmeticians were right. He needed them. We
needed them. This is fundamental
Buddhism. We should know 5, 5, and a bunch of them. We
should know 6 and 12 forces. We should
know 4 truths. But this is just
fundamental Buddhism. It continues. Do
you know why these three parts,
33 chapters, 3, 4, and 5, are
fundamental Buddhism. Seven hundred years ago,
what happened during these 70 years?
Nagarjuna happened. Nagarjuna happened.
You have this feeling.
Who will defeat these arithmeticians of Nagarjuna?
Let's do something cool. Give us something cool. The
emptiness of fasting
before fasting. That simplicity.
Or something like that. Right? After seven hundred years,
he came and completely changed Buddhism.
You know, Buddhism is not just that. It's
all just monks. Seven hundred years of
boring monks. The monks
simply repeated the list and that's it. And after
that time, Nagarjuna came. They
were called him tea.  Suji, the inventor of
the wheel, the discoverer of the wheel, the discoverer of the
wheel, he shook it all up. Let's
do it. He didn't say, let's
do it in a new way. He said, let's
go back to real Buddhism. Let's
go there. What will I
actually talk about? What was he actually talking about?
Emptiness and bodhichitta.
Arithmetic. Are you sure you realize
that all people are dying. That the whole world is on
fire. That hundreds of people are dying of hunger and
war. Why are you making a list? What nonsense?
Do something that will help people,
living beings, pain? Let's stop counting,
appearing and making a list. Let's
go to life.
Let's go back to love. If you
give strength to [ __ ], strength. If you follow
your morals, you will be happy. If
you are patient,
you will be beautiful. If you
enjoy your work, you will be happy. You will
be a leader. If you meditate,
[music]
your mind will be calm. If you study
wisdom, you will be liberated by love or
broken. All these things,
focus on love. Who said this? I'll be upset.
He just blows it all up in the
first three chapters.  In this course, there
comes a change in the archi on Yanyk Mahayana
love compassion cares and people
use emptiness and
to save people in this
book in this chapter he breaks it all
switches
[music]
you must realize this it's like
music I think that we need his yoga lesson and the
text is not to I told him that his
daughter and wait at the festival
races for such well I don't know maybe she
flour
similar to the unofficial flour from and her name is
Amelie and her official name is Amelie she is very
beautiful.  Nik-Nika she is very
beautiful and so and the text is not to
let's not disturb this
Nagarjuna
uses Hinayana to teach emptiness
he uses these verses using to
teach and add another to the eggs on emptiness
and then it turns out waving how much
time we have left seven minutes I
'll try to do this I will do the 2nd section
was about and no there is no own nature
[music]
rather there is nothing here is an aspirin that can
take away your main pain inflammation there is
nothing that can take away your
headache and so just like he thinks that your husband
is upset with you and because of something there is
nothing aspirin during the day nothing
that can take away your main pain
what is the proof
it doesn't work always don't get on a
plane I am the essence part of the time it doesn't
work because you will fall die you
won't want a plane that doesn't work
always don't continue taking aspirin
if 3 half part of the time it doesn't
work
understand how to work this is called
emptiness I am in the kingdom of carbon 3 for
slippery under the word atman and t a b n a t
atman it is very well known that he has
some happy something chemical inside
active ingredient is cancellation atman
means something inside that makes
things work nature itself something that
is inside makes itself work before thing
that doesn't work in Sanskrit
suit in Wisconsin [ __ ] is called
deception for Hindu people atman can be
god
so no no don't go to your friends
and tourists don't say that there is no cancellation cancellation
is bad aspirin just
respect the words atman
god we say that this thing inside and
chairs that makes it work
which doesn't exist but no
chemicals you look no say a
means no in Sanskrit is long
and in Sanskrit means no in English
and atheist don't believe in God
and you don't undertake any news yet
closes losses not interesting but
will follow I'm interested atheist not
religious in Greek also has this
long means no home volume means
to divide or separate something that in an
atom this thing that could not
cannot be divided also that you cannot
divide it becomes  Adom
Altman and also relates to this, the word
temple also comes from the height, no there
because in the old days, since it should
be far from the village, the temple should be
far from the green from the village from the
populated area, a
separate place is divided, this is something from this,
and there, perhaps, yoga will have to be shortened,
someone sees yoga, I will continue, admit,
put the boys cannot fight on the
splits and we have one of you, the pastors
for us are two parts, but people and the emptiness of
things is a big topic in on, they don’t even
really like this topic to burden his
emptiness and cracks, an illusion for 50 dollars,
and where for the emptiness in the kitchen, where are 2 emptiness
in the kitchen, by the way
[music]
come on, and his wife
70 to the top,
that is, the wife and husband are one emptiness and the
peasants are another, the
real answer in the kitchen of a person is the husband
who I did nothing, this is possible, it
exists, this is the emptiness of a person’s legs
walked, but there is evidence that from that he is
angry, a
red face, a loud sound, it is definitely
proven, so to speak, that
0 color, complexion and sound  Voices, wrinkles,
this is all real, a knife that I didn't
do anything about, it doesn't exist, but
look at the main ones, the red face
[music],
wrinkles,
this is all real, the person isn't real, I
understand, but I don't know, I didn't
do anything, but who made his face, the
size of Steve, didn't do it,
he took it himself, wrinkled face, wrinkled her
face, red, and for everyone, he says, I'm for
Parikshit, the
States smells bad here, something's not
quite right, this is called the emptiness of
things, with a red face, a loud sound,
wrinkles, this is the emptiness of things, where does this
red face come from? 0 dollars, who
created the red face, how did you have a
red face? Sometimes, the world of children,
the commission decided to look at yourself
when you yelled at the children, you had a
red face, the pieces
were also created by you, and the whole
was also conscious with the whole, and to marry about the
pieces, this red face, and so on,
now you know, at home, the connection, the entire
structure of wisdom, it's the wire, these two
types of emptiness, and people and things, what will we
talk about in the water section at the competition,
want to guess, the whole, 0 dollars, 50
write, chance for you in any case, up to the body part
[music]
feeling we discuss eyes this is the first of the
proud eyes to the 1st chapter of the university and eyes
each time parikshit he takes the most
important and fluid body pallet then 5
elements he focuses on
space very sections when he takes the sense
organs darma says 90 percent
one bare 90 percent of human
experience visually most often you judge
people not by smell but only if it is not
very strong but then you do not look
all suite as taught your eyes if
the eyes see things with the very essence of its
own nature then they always
see everything with if the eye visit if aspirin
treats yes it should cure everything when
in front of the card when it does not work then
someone behind her who says this is a
country this kind of worries me
there is an active ingredient in
fact it is there but it does not work
something here that worries me
imposes if in aspirin there is from us
if there is not something inside
that takes away your headache then you
need to always work if
your eye has something then it should
see everything always and should see that it
costs 98 dollars  76 last must believe the
eye I glass from we then your eye
must see when you look at the
beautiful sky
you should also see your own
eye if there is something that you do not see with
your eyes then the
eye does not see just like aspirin I do not
work then it does not work at all
as you think and if the eye if there is
if you something that the eye cannot see
then the eye also does not work as you
think the
eye does not see things get used to it
your eyes do not do anything you helped with the
flower people my mom I am very proud of
her 1 of 2
she is losing sight on one side
and Onagawa wants to help I am going to
help once a week with any people
teaches how to read the blind reading method and
makeup you are cool and her eyes are
improving why the eye sees because
you helped other people believe things
meter such a zama connection with chemicals and with
these cubes balls you see
because you gave the opportunity to see to others
you cared about the eyes of other people
[music]
I take it do you know where another
question accountant 11 comes back comes
back here I would like to make a
suggestion eye as well as fire eye
how  Fire, fire, only when kindling, burns
other things. The number lies itself. If
the fire had lit itself, then there would
be no fire. The god is sitting, and
therefore Nagarjuna, if something
does something, it does not mean that he must
do the same for himself.
Otherwise, there would be fire. There would be a yellow golf. And now,
as it is imposed, and what does he answer? I will not
tell you, but you are very lucky. Translated into
English, I want your
responsible homework to be about the
door. The channel is you go to the door.
You have a hint. There is a question for
homework. What is the contour? The argument that
gives it? And it is clear that the lawns are there, and you must
connect this with walking to the door. I am not
helping you. Your
fairy tale is all this. Don't forget. I looked
at
[music]
and
carry
[music].
The price is
flying [
music].
Carry
[music].
If